<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Depression Bear</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="pop_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="pop_desc">0 to 4 : No Depression or just Sad\n5 to 9 : Mild Depression\n10 to 14 : Moderate Depression\n15 to 19 : Moderate to Severe Depression\nmore than 20 : Severe Depression</string>
    <string name="agreement">This application will be used to detect Depression. \nIn the end we will provide a score and personal recommend activities to help you reducing depression.\nDisclaimer: This is not a diagnosis. This is a screening to give you an idea.</string>
    <string name="Question1_en">Little interest or pleasure in doing things</string>
    <string name="Question2_en">Feeling down, depressed or hopeless</string>
    <string name="Question3_en">Trouble falling or staying asleep, or sleeping too much</string>
    <string name="Question4_en">Feeling tired or having little energy</string>
    <string name="Question5_en">Poor appetite or Over eating</string>
    <string name="Question6_en">Feeling bad about yourself or that you are a failure or have let yourself or your family down</string>
    <string name="Question7_en">Trouble concentrating on thing, such as reading the newspaper or watching television</string>
    <string name="Question8_en">Moving or speaking so slowly that other people could have noticed</string>
    <string name="Question9_en">Thoughts that you would be better off dead or of hurting yourself in some way</string>
    <string name="Question1_cn">"做任何事都觉得沉闷或者根本不想做任何事"</string>
    <string name="Question2_cn">情绪低落、抑郁或者绝望</string>
    <string name="Question3_cn">难以入睡，容易惊醒；或相反睡觉时间过多</string>
    <string name="Question4_cn">觉得疲倦或者没有活力</string>
    <string name="Question5_cn">胃口极差或饮食过量</string>
    <string name="Question6_cn">不喜欢自己，觉得自己做的不好，对自己失望</string>
    <string name="Question7_cn">难以集中精神做事</string>
    <string name="Question8_cn">反应迟钝，或者比平常活动更多</string>
    <string name="Question9_cn">有自杀或者自残的想法</string>
    <string name="Question1_ru">нет интереса делать что-либо или трудно</string>
    <string name="Question2_ru">Чувство подавленности, депрессии или безнадежности</string>
    <string name="Question3_ru">Проблемы с засыпанием или слишком много спать</string>
    <string name="Question4_ru">Чувство усталости или мало энергии</string>
    <string name="Question5_ru">Плохой аппетит или слишком много еды</string>
    <string name="Question6_ru">Чувствовать себя плохо о себе - или что ты неудачник или подвел себя или свою семью</string>
    <string name="Question7_ru">Проблемы сосредоточиться на вещах</string>
    <string name="Question8_ru">Двигаться или говорить так медленно, чтобы другие могли заметил? Или наоборот - быть таким беспокойным или беспокойным что вы двигались намного больше, чем обычно</string>
    <string name="Question9_ru">Мысли о том, что тебе лучше умереть или причинить боль себя каким-то образом</string>
    <string name="to4">No Depression or just Sad</string>
    <string name="to4_cn">您当前状况良好</string>
    <string name="to9">Mild Depression</string>
    <string name="to9_cn">轻微抑郁</string>
    <string name="to14">Moderate Depression</string>
    <string name="to14_cn">中度抑郁</string>
    <string name="to19">Moderate to Severe Depression</string>
    <string name="to19_cn">中度抑郁至严重抑郁</string>
    <string name="more20">Severe Depression</string>
    <string name="more20_cn">严重抑郁</string>
    <string name="phq_9">This mobile application has been develop to detect depression based on Patient Health Questionnaire 9 (PHQ-9), Inc. No permission required to reproduce, translate, display or distribute. Data collected will be anonymous and will be used for just research related to depression.</string>
    <string name="terms">This app is for non-commercial use and only used for research purpose.</string>
    <string name="selection1_cn">从来没有</string>
    <string name="selection2_cn">有些时候</string>
    <string name="selection3_cn">超过一半的时候</string>
    <string name="selection4_cn">几乎每天</string>
    <string name="selection1_ru">никогда</string>
    <string name="selection2_ru">иногда</string>
    <string name="selection3_ru">больше половины дня</string>
    <string name="selection4_ru">почти каждый день</string>
    <string name="question_next_cn">下一题</string>
    <string name="question_next_ru">следующий</string>
    <string name="question_next_en">Next</string>
    <string name="selection1_en">Not at all</string>
    <string name="selection2_en">Several days</string>
    <string name="selection3_en">More than half days</string>
    <string name="selection4_en">Nearly Every days</string>
    <string name="landing_takeTest_en">Have you taken this Depression Test? </string>
    <string name="landing_takeTest_cn">请问您有做过抑郁症测试吗? </string>
    <string name="landing_diagnosis_en">Have you been diagnosis as Depression?</string>
    <string name="landing_diagnosis_cn">请问您有被诊断为抑郁症吗?</string>
    <string name="landing_gender_en">Gender</string>
    <string name="landing_gender_cn">性别</string>
    <string name="landing_age_en">Respondent Age</string>
    <string name="landing_age_cn">年龄</string>
    <string name="landing_createProfile_en">Create Your Profile</string>
    <string name="landing_createProfile_cn">建立您的个人档案</string>
    <string name="landing_yes_en">Yes</string>
    <string name="landing_yes_cn">是的</string>
    <string name="landing_no_en">No</string>
    <string name="landing_no_cn">没有</string>
    <string name="result_yourStats_en">Your Current Mind Status is:</string>
    <string name="result_yourStats_cn">您当前的抑郁状况为:</string>
    <string name="result_send_en">Send Result to Email</string>
    <string name="result_send_cn">保存结果</string>
    <string name="result_act_en">Recommend Activity</string>
    <string name="result_act_cn">推荐活动</string>
    <string name="activity1_title_en">Go for a thirty minutes walk outside</string>
    <string name="activity1_desc_en">You have answered in the test that you struggle doing things often, with little pleasure or interest. Walking can help decrease the effects of depression and being active is important for your body to stay healthy, which in return will give you more energy into doing things day to day.</string>
    <string name="activity2_title_en">Listen to upbeat/relaxing music</string>
    <string name="activity2_desc_en">You have answered that you feel down and hopeless often in the test. Listening to music is known to relax a person and clear their mind, creating a positive effect to your mental health.</string>
    <string name="activity3_title_en">Go to bed before 10pm</string>
    <string name="activity3_desc_en">You have answered that you trouble falling asleep, or sleep too much in the test. Resetting your body clock with going to bed early will help deal with this. Going to bed early and resetting your sleeping schedule is known to effectively decrease levels of depression.</string>
    <string name="activity4_title_en">Take in sunlight for 30 minutes</string>
    <string name="activity4_desc_en"> You have answered that you feel tired or have little energy. Sunlight and vitamin D are known to help your body and your health. People who suffer with depression are known to sit at home and not go out, which leads to them losing their required regulation of sunlight to keep healthy and energised. You need some YOU time and have a relaxing time outside.</string>
    <string name="activity5_title_en">Wake up early in the morning and eat a healthy breakfast</string>
    <string name="activity5_desc_en">You have answered that you have a poor appetite or are overeating often in the test. Starting your day early and eating the appropriate food is known to create and appetite and setting a working clock</string>
    <string name="activity6_title_en">Look in the mirror and tell yourself “I am special”</string>
    <string name="activity6_desc_en">You have answered that you feel bad about yourself or you feel that you are a failure or let yourself or family down. Telling yourself every day that you are special, can eventually lead to self-esteem boost and belief in what you say. A person with depression will constantly put themselves down, but by telling themselves the opposite can lead to positive effects.</string>
    <string name="activity7_title_en">Draw for thirty minutes</string>
    <string name="activity7_desc_en">You have answered that you struggle with concentrating on things. Drawing is known to relax and clear the mind which can help with these problems as it promotes positive thinking about art and creativity.</string>
    <string name="activity8_title_en">Go to the library and read a book</string>
    <string name="activity8_desc_en">You have answered that you feel as if your are moving or speaking too slowly and people have noticed or the opposite – feel so fidgety and relentless. Reading clears the mind and helps with concentration. This is extremely beneficial with the problems the users face from this question. They can become more relaxed while reading.</string>
    <string name="activity9_title_en">Talk to someone close and tell them how you are feeling</string>
    <string name="activity9_desc_en">You have answered that you have thought that you are better off dead, or thinking of hurting yourself. Talk to someone to release these thoughts and avoid yourself from any pain or suffering mentally and physically.</string>

</resources>
